

PROFILE

Being a committed team player, want to be a part of a renowned organization, to contribute towards the growth of the organization, based on my expertise and to further my personal capabilities by learning from the new exposer within the structured framework of the organization.

CONTACT

E-MAIL: Mikeykamau222@gmail.com

PHONE:

+254797934037

LINKEDIN:

www.linkedin.com/in/michael-kamau-633790203/

GITHUB

https://github.com/mik284

ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS

Software development Coding, listening to music, playing basketball, researching and reading novels. Full stack developer Cloud architecture

MICHAEL KAMAU

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT CONSULTANT

Organization: ASTERISK LIMITED – (2019-2020)
Position: Internship Period: 3 months

IT TECHNICAL DEPARTMENT

Organization: SLOPES MEDIA HOUSE – (2020-2021)
Position: Internship Period: 7 months

NETWORKING/CYBER SERVICES

Organization: Phyjos Systems LTD. (2022) Position: Internship

Period: 3months, Current

EDUCATION

Kenya Technical Trainers college/PC Kinyanjui Technical college

2019 – 2022- Graduated with a Diploma in information communication Technology

Lari Boy's High School

2015 - 2018 KCSE Grade C plain

Muchatha Primary School

2006 - 2014 KCPE Examination

KEY SKILLS AND CHARACTERISTICS

- Computer literate familiar with: MS Office, Internet & E-mails.
- Well-developed and effective communication skills.
- Management skills like meeting objectives, promoting solutions.
- Programming languages: HTML, HTML5, CSS, C++, C, JAVA, JAVASCRIPT, PYTHON, SQL, VISUAL BASIC
- Programming framework like: LARAVEL, BOSTRAP
- Computer software and hardware skills proficiency
- Other knowledge gained from self-learning; Git, GitHub, Unix commands, vim, AWS, Digital Ocean.